The William Siegmann Collection, 1932-2007 IULC038 IULC038
Liberian Collections
The William Siegmann Collection
1932-2007
Liberian Collections
Siegmann, William
IULC038
34.5 cubic feet; 35 records cartons
William Siegmann was the leading expert on the arts in Liberia and Sierra Leone. His collection contains an exhaustive lists of resources, both primary and secondary, pertaining to the arts, culture, language, and history of Liberia and Sierra Leone. Also included are materials from his various projects, espeically those from his "Aesthetics of Power: African Art Along the Windward Coast." Correspondence with various museums and universities, personal and teaching materials are also in this collection.
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions for this collection.
Accession Information
Closed for research.
Biographical History
William C. Siegmann ( 1943-2011 ) was a leading expert on the arts of Liberia and Sierra Leone and was particularly associated with West African masking traditions and performance. His interest was not only in their aesthetics, but in understanding the cultural meanings and context of these arts, including their relationship with cosmology, music and dance. During his career, Siegmann served as a curator at the Africana and National Museums in Liberia, Museum of the Society of African Missions African Art (NJ), Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco, and the Brooklyn Museum. He wrote and lectured extensively on the art of masquerades in Liberia and Sierra Leone, as well as on issues in museology, collecting, interpretation and connoisseurship. Siegmann shared his skills in collections development broadly, conducting frequent seminars on museum management and curatorial training in Europe, Africa, and South America. Both Siegmannâs papers and photographs are held by the Indiana University Liberian Collections.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into six series: Correspondence, Projects, Research, Subject Files, Teachings, and Writings. Many of the materials in the Research series are photocopies of original materials dating back to the 16th century. When possible the original date is inlcuded in parenthesis with the title
Scope and Content
The Correspondence series contains mostly personal exchanges with friends and colleagues. Prominent names in this series include Svend Holsoe, Warren d'Azevedo, and Andreas Massing.
The Projects series is divided into further subseries: "Aesthetics of Power: African Art Along the Windward Coast", Art of the Cavalla River, Brooklyn Museum, Louisiana World Expo,; SMA Fathers, and Subject Files. "Aesthetics of Power: African Art Along the Windward Coast" was an exhibition Siegmann worked on while he served as Research Associate in the Department of Africa, Oceania & The Americas at the Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco. It consists of correspondence with museums, galleries, and individuals concerning the African art works in their holdings, grant proposals to the National Endowment for the Humanities, and funding proposals to private institutions. Files may also include photographs, or photocopies of photographs, and collection appraisals and inventories.
The Research series encompasses all areas of interest for Siegmann. Most of this series is divided into subseries and includes extensive materials on art, linguistics, secret societies, education, culture, and politics.
The Subject Files series includes published materials (magazines, etc), personal ephemera, conference information, materials about the Liberian civil war and other miscellaneous materials.
The Teachings series has materials from Cuttington College, where Siegmann taught, as well as student papers.
The Writings series includes published materials, drafts, and reviews of Siegmann's work.
Acquisition Information
Donated by William Siegmann
Copyright Transferred
Copyright interests for this collection have been transferred to the Trustees of Indiana University. For more information, contact the Indiana University Liberian Collections
Art, Liberian; Art, West African; Bassa language (Liberia and Sierra Leone); Colonization; Dan (African people); Kpelle (African people); Kru (African people); Liberia--Civilization; Liberia--Economic conditions; Liberia--Description and travel.; Liberia--Languages; Liberia--Politics and government.; Liberia--Social conditions.; Linguistics; Loma language; Mano (African people); Museums; Museology; Secret societies; Liberia; Sierra Leone; Siegmann, William; D'Azevedo, Warren L.; Holsoe, Svend E.; Brooklyn Museum; African Art Museum of the S.M.A. Fathers; Cuttington College and Divinity School; Cuttington University College. Africana Museum; Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco; Louisiana World Exposition (1984) (New Orleans, La.); National Endowment for the Humanities
- Correspondence
  - A, undated, 1965-1988
  - Adams, [Monni], 1978
  - Addie and Dad, undated, 1965-1986
  - Addie, undated, 1978-1990
  - African Studies Program - Indiana University, undated
  - Auld, Lynne, 1982
  - B, undated, 1970-2005
  - Ben-Amos, Paula, 1979
  - Berney, Karen & Rex,, undated, 1990-2003
  - Biggane, Ed, 1976-1991
  - Bloh, D. Lincoln, 1974-1978
  - Bolay, Fatorma K., 1977-2003
  - Bolay, Joseph N., 1980-2004
  - Bolay, Samuel V., 1968/1970
  - C, undated, 1969-2006
  - Carter, Jeanette,, undated, 1969/1994
  - Carter, Keith, 1975-1992
  - Cornell, Robert, 1988-1992
  - Cuttington College & Divinity School, 1969-1983
  - D, 1969-1997
  - d'Azevedo, Warren, 1970-1997
  - de la Crus, Pedro "Poppy",, undated, 1979
  - Dietz, Kingdom, 1977
  - E, 1980-1986
  - Eicher, Joanne B, 1979
  - Epp, Edward,, undated, 1983-1984
  - F, 1976-1992
  - Fatima, 1975-1990
  - Flumo, John, 1969-1992
  - Fraker, Anne, 1979-1981
  - G, 1969-2002
  - Gardi, Bernard
  - Gay, John and Judy, 1969-1992
  - Government Invitations, 1968
  - H, 1969-2001
  - Himmelheber, Hans
  - Holiday Cards, 1969-1999
  - Holday Cards, undated
    General
    2 folders
  - Holsoe, Svend, 1973-1992
  - I, 1973-1986
  - J, 1968-1992
  - Johnson, Barbara, 1968-1987
  - K, 1983-1986
  - Kaba, Talli,, undated, 1971-1973
  - Kollie, John, 1975-1979
  - Koluba, John, 1974-1975
  - L, 1968-1999
  - Liberia. Ministry of Finance (Byron), 1969-1991
  - Liberia. National Bureau of Culture and Tourism, 1970-1974
  - Liberian Rubber Development Unit, 1983
  - M, 1969-2000
  - Martin, Jane, 1987-1988
  - Massing, Andreas,, undated, 1970-1986
  - McCollum, John, 1979-1980
  - Miscellaneous, 1969-1992
  - Miscellaneous, undated
  - Mount, Sigrid and Joe, undated, 1976-1986
  - N, 1969-2006
  - O, 1969-1986
  - P, 1969-1992
  - Phebe Hospital and School of Nursing, 1990-2003
  - R, 1969-1991
  - Ramsey, James R., 1979-1992
  - Robison, B., 1979-1992
  - S, 1971-1990
  - Seligman, Tom, 1969-1975
  - Sieber, Roy and Sophia, 1975
  - Siegmann, Bill,, undated, 1965-1991
  - Siegmann Ph.D Letters of Introduction, 1968-1975
  - Stanley, Janet, 1990-1995
  - Steve/Stephen, 1978-1986
  - Stone Rutg and Verlon, 1974-1991
  - T, 1968-1999
  - Togba, Phillip K., 1969-1999
  - Tolbert, William R., 1974
  - Tompkins, Karen, 1974-1988
  - U, 1986-1987
  - V, 1971-2007
  - W, 1973-2007
  - Warlobah, James E., 1979-1992
  - Williams, Wayne & Marge, 1973-1975
  - Yond, Richard, 1987-1991
  - Z, 1986-1990
- Projects
  - Aesthetics of Power: African Art Along the Windward Coast
    - Colleges and Universities
      - Beloit College, 1980
      - College of William and Mary, undated
      - College of Wooster, 1979-1980
      - Cuttington College, 1982-1983
      - Dartmouth College, 1980
      - Duke University, 1979
      - Georgia Institute of Technology,, undated, 1982
      - Harvard University,, undated, 1978-1983
      - Howard University,, undated, 1979
      - Indiana University,, undated, 1982
      - Lincoln University,, undated, 1979
      - Michigan State University, 1979
      - Morgan State University, 1979
      - Moscow State University, undated
      - New University of Ulster, 1982-1983
      - Oakland University, undated
      - Oberlin College, 1979
      - Princeton University, undated
      - State University of New York at Binghampton, undated
      - Universita Degli Studi di Roma, 1980
      - University of California, Los Angeles,, undated, 1979
      - University of Cambridge,, undated, 1980
      - University of East Anglia, 1980
      - University of Florida,, undated, 1979
      - University of Ghent`,, undated, 1980
      - University of Illinois,, undated, 1979-1982
      - University of Iowa,, undated, 1979-1980
      - University of Kiel, 1980
      - University of Michigan, 1979
      - University of Missouri - Columbia, 1979
      - University of Oslo, undated, 1980-1984
      - University of Oxford, 1980
      - University of Sierra Leone, 1980
      - University of South Dakota, 1979
      - University of Vermont, undated
      - University of Washington,, undated, 1978-1982
      - University of Zurich, undated
      - Universitat Basel, 1982-1983
      - Uppsala universitet, 1980
      - Yale University,, undated, 1979
    - Corporate Sponsorship and Funding
      - ARCO International Oil and Gas Company, 1982
      - Atlantic Richfield, 1982
      - BF Goodrich, 1980
      - Business Committee for the Arts, 1981
      - Citibank N.A., undated, 1981
      - Corporate Proposal, 1981-1982
      - FAMSF Exhibition Funding Status, 1982
      - Firestone Tire and Rubber Company, 1980
      - Fluor Foundation,, undated, 1981
      - Foremost-McKesson, 1980
      - Goodyear, 1980
      - Granges A.B., 1981
      - Heublein, undated
      - IBM, 1980
      - International Bank,, undated, 1980-1982
      - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1981-1982
      - Kodak, undated
      - The Liberia Company, undated
      - Liberia Consul General,, undated, 1982
      - List of Potential Donors, undated, 1982
      - Miscellaneous, undated, 1982
      - Miscellaneous Companies, undated, 1982
      - PepsiCo, 1980
      - Phelps-Stokes Fund, undated, 1982
      - Philip Morris, 1980-1984
      - Phillips Petroleum Company, 1982
      - Polaroid, 1981
      - Shell Companies Foundation, 1980
      - Sources and Funding, undated, 1980-1982
      - Standard Oil Company of California,, undated, 1981-1982
      - Stanley, Maxwell, 1980
      - Tempesman, Maurice, 1980-1981
      - Time, Inc, 1981-1982
      - Uniroyal, 1980
      - United Technologies Corporation,, undated, 1980
      - White, Ian, 1979-1981
    - Correspondence
      - Bellman, Beryl,, undated, 1978-1984
      - Billestraet, A., 1980
      - Black, David, 1979
      - d'Azevedo, Warren,, undated, 1977-1983
      - deStryker, Louis, 1980
      - Doboyou, Samuel T., 1982
      - Gavigan, Mona, 1982-1983
      - Gaisseau, Pierre-Dominique, 1972-1982
      - Geary, Christraud,, undated, 1982-1984
      - Gibbs, James L., 1978-1982
      - Gray, David L., 1981-1983
      - Guimot, Philippe, 1980
      - Hacker, Leora, 1981
      - Holsoe, Svend,, undated, 1976-1980
      - Hommel, William L., 1974
      - Ingemann, Frances, 1982
      - Karnley, Isaac, 1978
      - Kerser, Peter, 1983
      - Kuhn, Helen, 1979
      - Leasia, Shelley, 1981
      - Marchese, Lynell, 1983
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1978-1983
      - Moore, Bai T, 1980-1982
      - Moore, Owen, 1982-1983
      - Parcell, Father Joseph, 1982
      - Sawyer, Amos, 1981
      - Stone, Ruth, 1980
      - Swing, William L., 1981-1984
      - Tarpeh, James Teah,, undated, 1981
      - Tarr, S. Byron, 1981
      - Wellmers, William, 1982
      - Wijkstrom, Olle,, undated, 1981
    - Galleries
      - Alexander-Suggs Gallery, 1980-1981
      - Arcade Gallery, 1978-1980
      - Donald Morris Gallery, undated
      - Everett Rassiga Inc, undated
      - Galerie Helene Kamer, 1980
      - Gallerie Carrefour, 1980-1983
      - Gallerie Concorde, 1979
      - Gallery DeRoche, undated
      - J.D. Fradet, undated, 1980
      - James Willis Gallery, undated
      - Japan House Gallery, 1981
      - L. Kahan Gallery,, undated, 1979-1980
      - Michael Roth Gallery, 1979
      - Miscellaneous, undated
      - Pace Gallery,, undated, 1980-1982
      - Paulo Morigi Gallery, undated, 1980-1982
      - Peter Natan Gallery, undated
      - Pickard Art Galleries, undated
      - Ralph Proctor Gallery II, undated
      - William Rockhill Nelson Gallery,, undated, 1979
      - Rolin Gallery, undated
      - Schoffel and Groux, undated
      - Shango Galleries, undated
      - Tepaske and Hurst, undated
      - Tribal Arts Gallery, undated
      - Valerie Franklin, 1979
      - Van de Velde Gallery, undated
      - Volta Place Gallery, undated
    - Museums
      - Afrika Museum (Netherlands), 1980
      - American Museum of Natural History,, undated, 1979
      - Baltimore Museum of Art,, undated, 1983
      - Barbier-Mueller Museum (Geneva, Switzerland), 1980-1982, undated
      - Birmingham City Museums and Art Gallery (England), 1980
      - Birmingham Museum of Art (Alabama. ), 1979
      - Black History Museum (Hempstead, NY), 1979
      - Boston Museum of Fine Arts, 1979
      - Bowes Museum (Durham, England), 1980
      - Braunschweigisches Landesmuseum (Braunschweig, Germany), 1980
      - Brooklyn Museum, 1981
      - Buffalo Museum of Science, 1979
      - Carnegie Institute Museum of Art, 1979
      - Chemin de Musee (Brussels, Belgium), 1980
      - Chicago Art Museum, 1979
      - City of Bristol Museum and Art Gallery (England), 1980
      - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1980
      - Denver Art Museum, 1978-1982
      - Denver Museum of Natural History, 1979
      - Des Moines Art Center, 1979
      - Detroit Institute of Arts,, undated, 1978-1982
      - Etnografisch Museum (Antwerp, Belgium),, undated, 1980
      - Etnografiska Museet (Stockholm, Sweden),, undated, 1980
      - Ethnographic Museum (Goteborg, Sweden), 1980
      - Ethnogrphic Museum (Budapest, Hungary),, undated, 1980
      - Field Museum of Natural History, 1980
      - Frilandsmuseet (Lyngby, Denmark), 1980
      - Glasgow Museums and Art Galleries, 1980
      - Hamburgisches Museum fur Volkerkunde,, undated, 1978-1983
      - Hancock Museum (Newcastle upon Tyne, England), 1980
      - Heimat-Museum (Germany), 1980
      - Historical Museum of Bern,, undated, 1981-1982
      - Holice Museum (Holice, Chzechoslovakia), 1980
      - Honolulu Academy of Arts, 1979
      - Horniman Museum and Library (London), 1980
      - Houston Museum of Fine Arts, 1979
      - Hunteriam Museum (Glasgow), 1980
      - Ilfracombe Museum (Devon, England), 1980
      - Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1982
      - International Committee for Literature Museums, 1980
      - Ipswitch Museums (England), 1979-1980
      - Koninklijk Instituut voor de Tropen (Amsterdam), undated, 1980
      - Koninklijk Museum,, undated, 1980
      - Linden-Museum (Stuttgart, Germany), 1970/1981
      - Long Beach Museum of Art, 1979
      - Lowie Museum of Anthropology (Berekely, California),, undated, 1982-1984
      - Massillon Museum (Ohio), 1979
      - Merseyside County Musuems (Liverpool, England), undated, 1980
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art,, undated, 1978-1986
      - Milwaukee Public Museum, 1979
      - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1978-1981
      - Miscellaneous Museum Holdings, undated, 1980
      - Montreal Museum of Fine Arts,, undated, 1980
      - Musee d'Angouleme (Angouleme, France), 1980
      - Musee d'Ethnographie (Antwerp, Belgium), undated
      - Musee d'Ethnographie (Geneva, Switzerland), 1973-1980
      - Musee d'Ethnographie (Neuchatel, Switzerland),, undated, 1980
      - Musee de l'Homme (Paris),, undated, 1980-1981
      - Musee de Trocadero (Paris), undated
      - Musee des Arts Africains et Oceaniens (Paris), undated
      - Musee de Grenoble (France), 1980
      - Musee Municipal d'Angouleme, undated
      - Musee Royal de L'Afrique Centrale (Tervuren, Belgium),, undated, 1980
      - Musees d'Histoire Naturelle et D'Ethnographie de la Rochelle, 1980
      - Museo Etnografico (Buenos Aires), 1980-1981
      - Museo Nacional De Etnologia (Madrid), 1980
      - Museo Nationale Preistoriao Ethnografico (Rome),, undated, 1980
      - Museu de Ethnologia Do Ultramar (Portugal), undated
      - Museum de la Rochelle, undated
      - Museum Folkwang (Essen),, undated, 1980
      - Museum fur Kunst und Kulturgeschichte der Hansestadt Lubeck, 1980
      - Museum fur Volkerkunde (Berlin), undated, 1980-1983
      - Museum fur Volkerkunde (Frankfort, Germany), 1980
      - Museum fur Volkerkunde (Vienna), 1980
      - Museum fur Volkerkunde Leipzig, 1980
      - Museum fur Volkerkunde und Schweizerisches (Basel, Switzerland),, undated, 1980
      - Museum of African American Art (Santa Monica), 1983
      - Museum of African Art (Washington D.C.),, undated, 1938-1983
      - Museum of Mankind (London),, undated, 1980-1982
      - Museum of Modern Art (New York City), undated
      - Museum Rietberg (Zurich),, undated, 1977-1984
      - Museum voor Land-en Volkenkunde (Rotterdam, Netherlands),, undated, 1980
      - Naprstkovo Museum (Prague), 1980
      - Narodni Muzeum (Prague), 1978-1980
      - National Museum of Denmark, 1980
      - National Museum of History and Technology (Washington, D.C.), undated
      - National Museum of Natural History (Washington, D.C.), undated
      - National Museum of Canada, 1979
      - Newark Museum ( New Jersey),, undated, 1979
      - New Brunswick Museum, 1979
      - New Orleans Museum of Art,, undated, 1980-1984
      - Niedersachsisches Landesmuseum Hanover, 1980
      - North Carolina Museum of Art, 1981-1983
      - Panstwowe Muzeum Etnograficzne (Warsaw, Poland), 1980
      - Peabody Museum of Natural History (New Haven), undated
      - Peabody Museum of Salem (Massachusetts), undated
      - Philadelphia Civic Center Museum,, undated, 1979-1980
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1982
      - Pitt Rivers Museum ( Oxford, England), undated
      - Powell Cotton Museum (Oxford, England),, undated, 1980
      - Rautenstrauch-Joest-Museum (Cologne, Germany), 1971
      - Reading Public Museum and Art Gallery Philadelphia), 1979
      - Rijkmusuem Voor Volkenkunde (Leiden, Netherlands),, undated, 1980
      - Rimini Museum (Italy), undated
      - Roemer Museum (Hildesheim, Germany), undated
      - Rome National Museum, undated
      - Royal Ontario Museum,, undated, 1979
      - Royal Pavilion (Brighton, England),, undated, 1980
      - Royal Scottish Museum, 1980
      - Safari Museum (Kansas), 1979
      - Saffron Walden Musuem (Essex, England), 1980
      - St. Louis Art Museum, 1980-1982
      - San Antonio Museum Association, 1979
      - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, undated
      - Science Museum (London), 1980
      - Seattle Art Museum,, undated, 1979-1984
      - Smithsonian,, undated, 1978-1979
      - Staatliches Museum Fur Volkerkunde (Munich, Germany),, undated, 1980
      - Stadisches Museum (Braunschweig, Germany),, undated, 1980
      - Stiftung St. Galler Museen (Switzerland),, undated, 1980
      - Tervuren Museum Belgium, undated
      - Textile Museum (Washington D.C.),, undated, 1979-1981
      - Thomas Burke Memorial Washington State Museum, 1979
      - Toldedo Museum of Art (Ohio),, undated, 1979
      - Town Docks Museum (Hull, England), 1980
      - Tubman Center of African Culture (Robertsport, Liberia), undated
      - Ubersee Museum (Bremen, Germany), 1980
      - Ulmer Museum (Ulm, Germany), 1980
      - Vatican Museum, 1980
      - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1979-1980
      - Volkenkundig Museum (Tilburg, Netherlands), 1980
      - Wellcome Historical Medical Museum (London), undated
    - Other Organizations
      - American Film Archives, 1979
      - Barnes Foundation, 1979
      - Center of Art and Communication, 1981
      - De Menil Foundation, undated
      - Episcopal Church Archives, 1981
      - F. Rolin and Company, Inc, 1981
      - Humanities Productions, 1979
      - Institut fur der Wisserschafflichen Film,, undated, 1981-1983
      - Istituto Italo-Africano, 1980
      - J. Camp Associates, 1980
      - Leeds Department of Leisure Services, 1980
      - Ministere de la Culture et de la Communication,, undated, 1980-1981
      - Ministry of Information, Culture, and Tourism (Liberia), 1981
      - New York Public Library -; Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture, 1981
      - Nuneaton Borough Council, 1980
      - Royal Commonwealth Society (London),, undated, 1980
      - Saks Fifth Avenue, 1979
      - Thouars Municipal Library, undated
    - Private Collections
      - Anspach, Ernst, undated
      - Armstrong, Robert Plant, undated, 1981
      - Banks, Robert, 1983
      - Belgium, undated
      - Breslow, Elizabeth Kay, 1981
      - Calderini, Edizioni, undated
      - Carter, Jeanette, undated
      - Clausmeyer Collection,undated
      - Dartevelle Collection, undated
      - Dierick, Patrick, undated
      - duChastel, Count Simon, undated
      - Fourquet, Andre, undated
      - France, undated
      - Germany, undated
      - Ginsberg, Mark,, undated, 1979-1984
      - Gillon, M.J.W., 1981
      - Goldet, Hubert, undated
      - Gunn, Harold, 1981
      - Harley, Mrs. George, undated
      - Harter, Pierre, 1980-1981
      - Herman, Joseph, undated
      - Himmelheber Collection, undated
      - Holtam, Jordan, 1980-1981
      - Isaacson, Gene, undated
      - Italy, undated
      - Itzikovitz, Max, 1982
      - Kerchache, Jacques, 1980
      - Kitay, Michael, 1979
      - Kjersmeier Collection, undated
      - Leyden, Brian,, undated, 1979-1980
      - Lommel, Andreas, undated
      - Los Angeles, undated
      - Mangio, Vittorio, 1980-1981
      - Meneghini, Mario, 1980-1981
      - Mestach, Willy, undated
      - Miller, Charles,, undated, 1981-1982
      - Milton, John, 1981
      - Mizuno, Norman, 1981
      - Monzino, Carlo, undated
      - Moore, William, undated
      - Moulinier, Serge, undated
      - Mueller, Alfred, undated
      - Muller, Josef, undated
      - Munro, Thomas, undated
      - Muensterberger, Werner, undated
      - Nelson, Howard, undated
      - Newman, Arnold, undated
      - Newman, Marry, undated
      - Newman, Richard, undated
      - New York, undated
      - Nicaud, Maurice, undated
      - Nokes, Neil, undated
      - Nooter Collection, undated, 1980-1983
      - Osborn, James, undated
      - Oklahoma City, undated
      - Pailes Collection, undated
      - Peissi, P., undated
      - Perlbinder, Mark, undated
      - Perutz, George, undated
      - Peters, Norman, undated
      - Philips, Christine,, undated, 1980
      - Picket, E., undated
      - Pinto, Morris, undated
      - Plass, Webster, undated
      - Prevost, Patrick, 1982
      - Price, Vincent, undated
      - Quint, Bernard, undated
      - Rasmussen, Rene, undated
      - Ratton, Charles,, undated, 1980
      - Robinson, Edward G., undated
      - Rody, Robert, undated
      - Rome, Harold,, undated, 1979
      - Rubenstein, Helena, undated
      - Rudngansky, I, undated
      - Sainsbury, Robert,, undated, 1980-1981
      - Sandoz, Edouard, undated
      - Sanfield, Philip, undated
      - Sarick, Samuel,, undated, 1975-1980
      - Scamperle Collection, undated, 1980
      - Schadler, Karl, undated
      - Schenk, Victor, undated
      - Schmidt Collection, undated
      - Schnell Collection, undated
      - Schoffel, Christine, undated
      - Schramm, Dorothy, undated
      - Schulze, Gary, undated
      - Segy, Ladislas, undated
      - Seibel, Elmar W., 1979
      - Seipp, Joseph, undated
      - Selenga, Francis, undated
      - Seligman, Tom, undated
      - Seylaz, Paul, undated
      - Shapiro Collection, undated
      - Sieber, Roy, undated
      - Silver, Edwin,, undated, 1973-1979
      - Silverman, Ira, undated
      - Silverman, Melvin, undated
      - Nancy Silverman, undated
      - Simpson, M., undated
      - Sorafin, Michael, undated